

DINH THI HUYEN

INTERNSHIP TESTER

Pemale



0971.832.902



May 15, 1993

dinhhuyen.vimaru@gmail.com

0

Xuan Dinh- Bac Tu Liem - Hanoi,

66

Short-term: Working in a professional, active and fairly competitive working environment and having opportunities to get promotion. Always improve myself and learn more new knowledge and skills while on the job, to pass ISTQB foundation and advance certificates

Long-term: Become Seninor Tester after 2 years

Education

Vietnam Maritime University, Major: Imformation Technology

Oct 2011 - Jan 2016

Akamonkai Nihongogakkou, Major: Japanses

Jun 2016 - May 2017

T3H Academy, Major: Manual Tester

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Work experience

FUTTO WAKU JSC (JAPAN), Sales Staff

JUNE 2017 - OCT 2020

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out. Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company
- Other requests from superiors

JAPAN - VIET NAM MECHANICAL AND BUILDING JSC, Sales Staff

NOV 2020 - DEC 2021

Main responsibilities:

- Sales activities for overseas customers
- Quotation preparation / document preparation
- Communication with factories and clients (ordering, delivery date management, etc.)
- Other requests from superiors

Skills

Language: Japanese N2

Computer: Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Project:

Position : Tester Description:

- Learn the service system, read the SRS specification document.
- Test design.
- Write test cases and proceed tests for functions: product management, management of product categories, management of promotions, management of customers, order management, supplier management, supplier's order management unit.
- Perform data query using SQL Server.

Tool: SQL Server, Redmine

Knowledge about:

- Software Development process.
- Experience in Software testing process.
- Business Requirement Specification, System Analysis
- Testing methods, Testing Levels, Testing Types
- Writing testing test cases
- Monitoring and recording results in test documentation.
- Using tools : SQL Server , Redmine

Additional information

- Adapting to the new working environment quickly
- Get the job done on time and efficiently
- Enjoy working as a team and can work in high pressure condition
- Enthusiasm, hard working, independent
- Honest, probity, out-going and humor